Zack, Arnold Additional Arbitration Files 5979
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Arnold Zack Additional Arbitration Files
1991-1994
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Zack, Arnold M.
5979
7 cubic feet
7 linear ft.
Papers, arbtitration decisions.
5745660
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, February 07, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 05, 2015
Biographical / Historical
Lawyer, arbitrator, and government official; LLB Yale, 1956, MBA Harvard, 1961, MA Harvard, 1963.
Arnold Marshall Zack is an arbitrator and mediator. Beginning his labor career as a part-time election examiner for the National Labor Relations Board and as a case analyst for the U.S. Wage Stabilization Board (1950-1953), he was also a lecturer in labor economics at Simmons College, Northeastern University (1957-1963); an assistant to Saul Wallen, arbitrator, (1956-1960); director of the Labor-Management Institute of the American Academy of Arbitrators (1966-1968); and has served in various labor-related international posts for the United States government.
Other governmental service includes membership on panels for the Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service, the Massachusetts Public Employment Relations Board, the New York State Public Employment Relations Board, The New Jersey Public Employment Relations Board, The New York City Office of Collective Bargaining, and The National Mediation Board. Zack is also a panel member of the American Arbitration Association, and has served as the permanent arbitrator for a number of major corporations and unions and for the State of New York and the U.S. Postal Service.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Zack, Arnold.
5745660
- W, Miscellaneous. (Box 1)
  - Tufts/SEIU 254 Boston, MA AAA Dec 1, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - S. Ct. Gas/USWA 120000 Dec 8 Stratford, CT, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Dye craftsmen/ ACTWU TBD (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Emhart Glass/Local 376 UAW June 8, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Exeter/FF Local 3491 June 30 Town Offices, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Ferrera & Sons/IBT 829 Nov 28, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - G. Portland/ATU 714 April 6, 1994 Portland, ME (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - W. Springfield Housing/AFSCME May 7, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - WMATA/Local 2 Sept 20, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Weare SD/NEA June 17, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - White Mt SD/education Association May 31, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Worcester/IAFF 1009 Feb 1 Worcesster City Hall, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Yardney Technical/IUE 431 June 10, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - UPS - Teamsters 776 Jan 10, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - US Immigration/AFGE 2711 Nov 9, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Warwick SD/Warwick Teacher's Union Sept 13, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Wash Transit/ Local 689 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Weare, NH (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Fact-Finding Brief of the Contoocook Valley Education Association (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Contoocook County salary, etc. (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Exhibits Keene State College Education Association (Box 1, Folder 21)
- L-N. (Box 2)
  - City of Lynn/IAFF Lynn, MA Oct 25, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - City of Lynn/IAFF, Local 739 City Hall, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - City of Lynn/Lynn Police Association (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - `St of Maine/ MSEA Sept 16, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Metro Life Ins./UFCWIU, March 14 AAA Hartford, CT, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - City of Medford/ IAFF Jan 26, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - New Britain SD/New Britain Fed of Tech March 1, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Natick SD/Education Association Nov 2 Natick, MA, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - New Boston factfinding April 11 NEA Manchester Office, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - IRS/NTEU March 29 & April 15 Brooklyn, NY, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Grotto Bay (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Littleton/Police Dept. April 12 town Hall, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - City of Holyoke/IAFF Feb 7, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - IRS/NTEU 68 March 28 April 14, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Kearsarge SD/ Educational Assoc. Jan 6, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - J. R. Hess/IBT Local 251 May 13, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Hartford Brd of Ed/Fed of Teachers March 16, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Hillsborough/AFSCME Hillsborough Bursting Home Feb 17, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Oct 6, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - University of NH/AAUP Aug 25, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - NYC board of Ed/United Fed of Teachers (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - James River/ UPIU (Box 2, Folder 22)
- O-S. (Box 3)
  - Semline, Inc./GCIU, Local 600M AAA Boston Feb 23, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Shaw's/UFCW 791 Braintree, MA Nov 30, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Shaw's/UFCW Local 791 Sept 12 Sheraton Tara Braintree, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Shaw's/UFCW, Local 791 Sheraton Tara Jan 20, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Shaw's/UFCW Local 791 Sheraton Tara Braintree April 28, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Shaw's/UFCW Local 791 Sheraton Tara Braintree May 2, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Shaw's/UFCW Local 791 Sheraton Tara Braintree June 15 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Rutland SB/Education Assoc, Rutland, VT Nov 10, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Town of Salem/Salem Police Town Hall Jan 24, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Shaw's/UFCW Local 791 Sheraton Tara Braintree June 1, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Sanborn SD/Regional Support Staff Superint Office Kingston, NH Sept 19, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Sanborn SB/Regional Educ. Assoc. Kingston, NH Nov 17, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Resthaven Nursing home/SEIU Nov 16 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Portsmouth Navy June 8, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - PSG, Inc. Case 11 300 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Providence Journal/Newspaper Guilg Prov. RI (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Opera House (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Philadelphia/Phil Police Phila, PA (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Ocean State Steel (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Pawtucket/RI AFSCME Pawtucket, RI (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Newton Wellesley Hospital/AMAOcean State Steel and United Steelworkers of America AFL-CIO-CLC (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Specialty Paperboard/UPIU, #1862 Brattleboro, VT 05301 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Teamsters Local 559 and Sweet Life Foods, Inc. (Box 3, Folder 23)
- A-E. (Box 4)
  - Endispute Mediation Boston, MA March 5, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - United Steelworkers/R. Derecktor of RI Middletown, RI (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Derry/IAFF Derry, NH Jan 24, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Town of Derry/IBPO #565 Feb 10 Derry, NH, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Continental Baking/BC&T AAA Boston Nov 17, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Champion Inc./IBT, Local 239 M Providence, RI May 14, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Charlesgate Nursing Home/NEHCEU Providence, RI Feb 26, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Cheshire County/SEIU Keene, NH May 17, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - City of Chicopee/Police Chicopee Dec 15, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Cambridge/IAFF, Local 30 Cambridge, MA March 23, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - National Mediation Board Burlington Railroad #5104 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Berlin Brd of Ed/Berlin Ed assoc Berlin, NH March 29, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Assoc Spring Div (Barnes) UAWA E. Hartford, CT June 11, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Banger School Comm/Ed. Assoc. Bangor, ME June 18, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Central Adams/Teacher's Assoc. Colorado May 10, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - American Tissue Mills/UPIU Gardner, MA Jan 29, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Anderson Power/UAW Dec 3, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Anderson Power/UAW, Local 1596 AAA Boston Dec 10, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Case No. PE-11-92, Late Postponement of Hearings on April 7 & 8, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - American Airlines/Pilots Nashville Airport June 29 & 30 Aug 16, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Lloyd Manufacturing/URW, 309 Providence, RI Nov 24, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - City of Lowell/Teamsters, 49 Chelmsford, MA June 22, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Lindeborough/Ed assoc. FF, NEA-NH Aug 26, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Laber Russo/IBTCWHA, Local 251 July 12, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Littleton/NEA-NH Mediation June 28, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Lexington/AFSCME 93 Lexington, MA Oct 20, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - James River/IUOE #877 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - IRS/NTEU March 9 & 10 Hartford, CT (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - UPIU, Local 1188 and Champion Paper company (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Brighton SD/Ed assoc. 8/19, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - SEIU Local 254 and Boston University (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Jewish Home/NEHCEU Providence, RI May 20, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Kanzaki Paper/UPIU, 708 W. Springfield, MA May 4, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- C. (Box 5)
  - Amesbury/IBPO #629 Amesbury Town Hall April 26, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - A.R.A. Services/Teamsters 1035 Jan 3 AAA Hartford, CT, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Barlett SB/Educ. Assoc. Aug 24, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Boston College/SEIU, #254 Nov 4 AAA Boston, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Bethlehem SB/Ed Assoc. Sept 21 SEA - Littleton, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Boston Edison/UWUA, Local 369 Feb 28, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - City of Cambridge/MNA Cambridge, MA March 11, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Cambridge Brands/IBFO Local 3 AAA Boston, MA, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - City of Cambridge/IAFF Local 30 Feb 11 City Hall, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Town of Canton/IBPO 465 Town Hall March 30, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Central ME Power/IBEW 1837 S. Portland, ME Aug 17, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Charlesgate Nursing Center/NEHCEU 1199 Providence, RI Jan 12, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Charlesgate/NEHCEU 1199 Nov 1, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Clarkstown/Teachers Assoc. May 3 Elmsford, NY, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Com Gas/BUWNE, Local 333 June 22 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - State of Connecticut (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - St. of Ct/NEHCEU 1199 Jan 4-5, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - St. of Ct/NEHCEU 1199 Jan 4-5, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Con Val SB/Con Val Education Assoc. Oct 26, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Conwway School Board/Education Association July 14, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Cytec/ICWU 436 Oct 6, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Danaher tool/Springfield, MA Nov 7, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Town of Derry/State Employ Assoc. Derry, NH Aug 18, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Durham/Teachers durham. NH Jan 12, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Park Plaza/HRE, Local 217 New Haven, CT Nov 23, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Park Plaza/HEREIU, #26 Boston, MA April 28-29, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Thomas Foods/BC&T, Local 348 AAA Boston Nov 11, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Tandet CeNTer/NEHCU 1199 Stamford, CT July 14, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Tarkett/IBT, Local 445 AAA White Plains, NY April 1, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Commerce City Denver, CO (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Miscellaneous. (Box 6)
  - Wellesley college/IMSEU Wellesley, MA Sept. 15, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Wellesley College/IMSE AAA Office Dec 4, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Waterbury Hospital/CT Health Care Ass Waterbury Dec 10, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Wash DC Transit March 22, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Urban Eng./IUOE Local 1877 Boston Copley Place Aug 18, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - UPS/Teamsters 776 Harrisburg, PA March 16, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Great Northern/UPIU 12 Millinocket, ME Dec 16 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Union Paper/USWA Local 4652-1 Providence, RI April 30, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Union Paper/USWA June 14, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Slater Health/NEHCEU1199 Providence, RI Oct 27, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - State of Maine MSEA Augusta, ME July 6, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Greater Portland Transit/ATU 714 Protland, ME Aug 24, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Presbyterian Hospital/Local 1199 June 10 NY, NY, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - State of NH v. SEA Feb 19+ 22, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Mayer Center/HERE 217 Providence May 27, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - State of Maine/MSEA Augusta, ME May 25, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - State of Maine/MSEA Augusta, ME May 11, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Marson Corp/UAW AAA Boston, MA May 26, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Maryland, Ocean City Nov 4, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Western Mass Electric/IBEW 455 Chicopee, MA Jan 4, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Wentworth Institute/Faculty Fed. Lincoln, MA Feb 17, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Wentworth Institute/Faculty Fed. Boston, MA AAA Dec 7, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Greater Portland Transit April 24, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Overhead Door/Iron Workers 57 Boston, Ma May 18, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Windham Hospital/Fed of Health Prof Willimatic, CT Oct 14, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Winnisquam School/Teachers Assoc. Winnisquam, NH April 2, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Windham Pepsi/Local 493 Hartford, CT Oct 20, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Yale New Haven Hosp/NEHCEU New Haven, CT Jule 13, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Yale New Haven Hosp/NEHCEU New Haven. CT May 13, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - City of Woburn/IBPO Woburn, MA Jan 13-14 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - TWA/IAM Nov 5, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - TWA JFK Holiday Inn, Jamaica, NY Aug 25, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Shaws/UFCW, Local 791 March 3 Braintree, MA, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 34)
- Miscellaneous. (Box 7)
  - Shaws/UFCW, Local 791 March 3 Braintree, MA, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Shaughnessy-Kaplan/AFSCME #93 July 16 Salem, MA, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Rockland/IBPO Rockland, MA May 3, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - RI Port Authority/IUOE 877 North Kingston, RI July 15, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Case No. 11 300 0136 92 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Portsmouth Naval/FEMTC Portsmouth, NH Sept 20, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Portsmouth Navy Yard/FEMTC Sept 22, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Portland Water/IBT 340 Nov 15, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Portsmouth Naval/FEMTC Portsmouth, NH Oct 18, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - SuperPlace/UFCW 328 Mansfield, MA Dec 13, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Stafford Brd of Ed./Ed. Assoc. Stafford Springs, CT March 2, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Stone & Webster/IFPTE AAA Boston June 23, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Slater Health Center/NEHCEU 1199 Pawtucket, RI (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Shaw's/UFCW 791 Braintree, MA July 7, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Shaw's/UFCW Local 791 Braintree, MA Spet 27, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - IRS/NTEU IRS Andover Sept 30, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Hillside Manor/NE Health Care Employees Hartford, CT March 6, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Hillsboro/Fed of Teachers June 9, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Heublein/DWW Local 1 Plainville, CT Sept 17, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Hamilton/Wenham School/AFSCME 93 S Hamilton, MA May 5, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Handy & Harman/United Steelworkers Stratford, CT Jan 15, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Hartford Bd of Ed/Hartford Teachers AAA Hartford, CT Feb 3, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - John Hancock/UFCW AAA Boston Nov 29, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - UPS/Teamsters 776 Harrisburg, PA Jan 28, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - RI Port Authority/IUOE 877 North Kingston, RI Nov 8, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 25)